Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
Three days later
Your messenger is coming, my Sultan.
Soldiers!
Wait!
Tell me.
My Sultan, as you command, Osman
Bey has welcomed me.
Your tent has been set up.
They are waiting for you.
Tell me, how are Ghazis?
Are the soldiers worried or cheerful?
My Sultan, all Gaziyans (a religious and
military team) are cheerful.
Osman Bey also is.
All Ghazis respect Osman Bey.
They say it's an honor for them...
to fight for Osman Bey's tent.
(There is no winner but Allah.)
Where are you, Aygül?
She will be here soon with my Bey.
Why are you so impatient, Cerkutay?
I am.
I am impatient than ever, brother.
I am walking on air.
We'll take revenge on Byzantine.
We'll take their ammunition.
And...
And?
I'll prepare a trousseau. (dowry)
I'll prepare a trousseau.
Alps.
What is the situation?
They kept changing their
places all night.
They are having a rest now. They will go
to military quarters at night.
They have lots of trophies and ammunition.
They look exhausted, my Bey.
We can walk all over them, my Bey.
They have lots of ammunition.
However, they are crowded too.
Should we tell Alps, Osman Bey?
Four to one, brother.
A wolf can harm four jackals.
Look.
Cerkutay is out of his patience.
Come on.
Sultan is about to arrive. We
shouldn't lose much time.
- Brother. Stay with the archers.
- Okay, Osman Bey.
Aygül Hatun will take care of others.
Okay, my Bey.
Allah is eternal!
Turks! Damn!
Battle order!
Osman is weak.
The battle will be his end.
I wish it was that easy, Dukas.
He has nothing to trust
except for Sultan's army.
He will trust the
thing he has trusted till today.
It's the first time that Sultan's
army is coming.
Those who lose their
hope before the war...
shouldn't join the battle.
I am sure that we'll win the war.
I don't know who will die or not.
The military camp has been
set up near Domaniç, sir.
What about the support unit? Ammunition?
They are there.
They will bring the ammunition to the
military quarters tonight.
Let's go then.
Victory is waiting for us.
Don't run away!
Die, Osman!
Say that to my sword.
My Bey.
Alps.
- You're happy, Cerkutay.
- Of course I am.
I was thinking about the dowery but
the emperor's army already prepared it.
It's time for you to marry a halal Hatun.
Yes, my Bey.
Yes.
Osman Bey.
Dukas and Nikola will be surprised...
when they learn about the
ammunition and support unit.
- However, Leo...
- They don't know about Leo.
They trapped us.
However...
I will punish Dukas during the war.
- Göktuğ!
- My Bey.
Bring the ammunition to
Sultan's military quarters.
Your command, my Bey.
Let's go.
Come on.
- How are you?
- I'm fine, Ayşe Hatun.
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
Malhun Hatun, we heard that
you're pregnant.
May Allah let your child grow up with
his/her mother and father.
We have gifts for you.
Thank you, Hatuns.
Thank you.
Come here, let's drink our Sherbet
and talk.
Zoe, bring Sherbet to our guests.
Mashallah.
Osman Bey has been waiting for
this good news for a long time.
Not just our Bey, also our tent.
Thank Allah we have seen these days.
Hatuns.
Everyone wants to know...
who their words are heard by.
If you excuse us.
I want to talk to you if you excuse me.
I have some work to do.
If you excuse me.
Zoe, Alaca.
Help me.
What's the matter, Bala Hatun?
Zoe.
I suspect her.
Why?
She told Gonca that she went to
a draper store in Söğüt.
However, she didn't.
Not just that.
She disappears a lot.
Be careful.
Does Osman Bey's Hatun...
spy out the woman who helps me?
You're angry because
I let Zoe in the tent.
However, you don't have to worry.
I trust her.
I told you what I thougt.
It's up to you now.
Soldier!
What happened?
What happened, soldier?
All of the soldiers are dead.
- What about the ammunition?
- They took it.
Damn you, Osman!
You were wondering why
Osman didn't respond to our raid.
That's why!
- We've lost our superiority!
- We are still superior.
We've lost the support
unit and the ammunition.
I've sent them in
two different ways!
Helen must have sent the other
half of the ammunition to the quarters.
Talk.
Sultan's army is about to
arrive.
To the horses!
Alps!
Get ready!
Welcome, my Sultan.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Thank you, Sheikh.
You adorn Osman Bey's army.
Thank you, my Sultan.
Even though our hands are weak
because of the swords...
our prayers are strong.
Our prayers...
are our strongest shields.
Yes.
I know your situation.
We will win with Allah's help!
Inshallah, my Sultan. La galibe illallah!
(There is no winner but Allah.)
Let's go.
Helen, did the support unit
and ammunition arrive?
Yes, as you command.
The villagers are bringing supplies.
Don't trust the villagers.
Don't let them enter the quarters.
Sir, Sultan arrived in
the quarters with his army.
Come and see, Sultan Mesud.
The Byzantine quarters...
(headquarters/military quarter)
will be behind the
Çarıklıtepe. (Çarıklı hill.)
The Byzantine army will come to the
battlefield right this way.
Here is the battlefield.
What worries me is the ammunition
that the Byzantine emperor has sent.
The Emperor has a good army.
We have the ammunition
of Byzantine, my Sultan.
Don't worry.
How?
We checked every route
leading to the quarters.
We located them and got it.
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey.
You saved us.
Thank you, my Sultan.
Thank you.
However, I know that...
Nikola is wise as he won't send the
ammunition with just one unit.
My Sultan, it's big strike anyway.
Then...
tell me everything you
know about the enemy, Osman Bey.
The Byzantine army consists of two units.
Dukas' army...
and the cavalry of Nikola.
Malhun Hatun thinks you are her rival.
I hope we are wrong.
She doesn't know that I
can do everything...
for my Osman Bey's child.
My beautiful Bala.
What will we do about Zoe, my Bala?
If we are right...
it may harm Osman Bey.
We can't let that happen.
- Watch her.
- Don't worry, my Bala.
When our Bey and...
Boran comes back...
we will let them know.
Dukas will come from the
quarters to the battlefield.
He wants to circle us.
Our commanders who have witnessed
situations like that are among us.
Dukas is...
strong in pitched battles.
The Seljuqs army have
witnessed it so many times.
How many soldiers we have from
the new comers, Nikola?
350.
Their military education is done.
We will fight in order.
We won't let Turks harm us.
Dukas' biggest power is...
his army who can use shield masterfully.
The army we fight consists
of those people.
I agree with you, Osman Bey.
I will meet them in the center...
with my army who have shields.
On the left-wing, there will be
Emir Arslan's soldiers.
On the right-wing, you will fight there
with your Beys and Alps.
The war will start tomorrow.
We have so many soldiers, Commander Dukas.
Osman trusts Sultan's army, and Sultan
trusts the Turk Beys' Alps.
He will come with a strong army.
Osman holds himself in readiness.
We will attack from three sides.
The soldiers from Macedonia
will be in the center.
I will control the soldiers
from the left-wing.
Adnos will control the military units of
the governors on the right-wing.
Nikola will be the support unit
with his own soldiers.
It's an honor for me to fight next
to a big commander like you.
What about you, Nikola? Is there
anything you will say?
We outnumber them. We
are superior to them. However...
if we don't think of
Turks' archers...
we lose the war.
What are your plans?
Does anyone have a word to say?
May our war be holy, my Sultan.
May Allah help us.
Amin.
Osman Bey...
I have things to say.
I see that you have a strong
connection with the Beys.
You manage them well.
My Sultan, our lands are
under the Mongols' attack.
My Beys know that...
if our unity is ruined, we will not
only lose...
but also we will fall apart.
We will win, Inshallah.
They would know if they saw your Ghazis...
who are very eager to fight.
Inshallah, my Sultan.
Inshallah.
Can I come in, Osman Bey?
Come in, brother.
Come and sit.
Osman Bey, I looked at the
Alps as you command.
They are ready and eager to fight.
Thank you, brother.
Thank Allah that you are happy
as you will have a child.
Inshallah, everything will
be good, brother.
Amin, brother.
Amin.
There are others as well who are happy
to know that you will be a father.
Yes.
All Muslims and non-Muslims
in the tents, villages...
are so happy.
Do you know why?
Because they see their
future in you, Osman Bey.
In you and in your children who will born.
Everything we do for Allah...
is also for our children and descendants.
- May Allah bless them.
- Amin, brother.
Brother.
I have to do something...
if you excuse me.
Come on, do it.
Thank you.
Come on.
Be careful.
I looked for you the other day.
You had a job to do.
Tell me, I can do that my Hanım.
It was an easy one.
Where were you that day?
I was going to the draper....
but I went to the church.
I gave the money you gave me
for my service to the Pope.
Why?
I said why, Zoe.
We donate the church for the
children who will be born.
It's a tradition.
We pray and light a candle on behalf of
Mother Mary for the child to be healthy.
The child?
I prayed for your child.
Everyone is looking at you.
You call that Nazar. (evil eye)
We call that Mati.
You carry a burden.
Why would my child be a burden, Zoe?
It has an evil eye on it.
You attract Nazar.
May God protect her from Nazar.
You attract Nazar from people
around Osman Bey.
Especially...
I also prayed to Mother Mary for Osman Bey
to come back from the war safe and sound.
Just for Osman Bey?
No one protected me ever.
I also prayed for my Bey who protected me...
and for my Hanım's Alps.
Amin.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahîm. (In the name
of Allah, the Merciful, the Compassionate)
May my Lord let you back in our tent...
with our child, my Bey.
Osman!
You are back, Osman Bey.
I wanted to see you before the war.
I am so glad you did.
Welcome.
How is our child?
Good, thanks to Lord.
I am fine too, Osman Bey.
Of course you are.
You should be good so that our child
can be good.
I'll heat water.
You shall rest.
Malhun Hatun, thank you.
But I have to go back.
Are you going back in nigh time?
It's full moon.
My horse will find his way.
You know what you need to do.
I would love to fight by your side in
this war.
You are already giving the
greatest fight...
my Lord mentioned.
Yes, right.
Malhun Hatun, get rest.
Protect yourself and our child.
Don't worry Osman Bey.
We'll be fine.
Our child is entrusted to Allah first,
then to me.
May your fight be blessed.
Osman Bey is here.
He is going to his tent.
Allah is the greatest. x4
I bear witness that there is
no god except the One Allah. x2
I bear witness that Muhammad
is the messenger of Allah. x2
Hurry to the prayer.
What are they doing?
- Hurry to the prayer.
- What every Turk does before war, Ducas.
- Hurry to salvation.
- They are seeking help from their god.
Hurry to salvation.
There is only one place
they'll go to, Niicola.
Under the soil where
they are going to rot.
Prayer is better than sleep.
Allah is the greatest. x2
There is no god except the One Allah.
Allah-u Akbar.
(Allah is the greatest.)
“Allah hears whoever praises Him.”
Allah-u Akbar.
(Allah is the greatest.)
"May the peace, mercy, and blessings of
Allah be with you."
Allah-u Akbar.
(Allah is the greatest.)
You have to suffer to get the victory!
We came here through the bloody paths!
We are going to drown
Turks in their blood!
If a soldier leaves fighting and starts
thinking...
no one will be left alive in the army!
My Allah, raise the flag of Islam!
- Help us.
- Amin.
Grant your valiants with your support
that fills our tents with security...
You strenghten the warriors who fight
for your name...
We sacrifice ourselves in your path,
we obey you all the time.
Amen!
Byzantine's brave sons!
I order you to die, not to think!
Death is a honor for us.
Losing without fighting is a dishonor.
Victory...
is with us!
Victory is with us!
Oh our Lord!
You are our trustee...
we smooth our faces over the ground
for you...
we fight in your name.
Bless our war.
Amen!
Allah-u Akbar.
(Allah is the greatest.)
I am the one who trapped you, Osman Bey.
I'll kill Leo after the war.
Save your swords!
Go forward!
Attack!
Allah-u Akbar.
(Allah is the greatest.)
Beat the drum!
Alps!
We are retreating!
Retreat!
Hurry!
They are retreating! We should
retreat too. We'll finish them tomorrow.
Soldiers!
We are retreating!
Retreat!
This should have been done today!
We should have pushed them
when they were retreating.
We had to scatter to chase them.
A scattered army is the only thing
Osman wants.
Isn't this right, Yason?
Which one of you have better soldiers
than his alps?
None of you!
Do not counsel!
We are not going to change our formation!
If we change our position, we'll be
hunted by Osman!
Sultan's army made it harder.
As Commander Ducas said, we'll finish this
tomorrow.
If we can't finish it tomorrow,
they'll end us.
How can you talk like that?
Enough!
It is no use to argue now!
It's not about Sultan and his army.
The issue is Osman.
Osman!
Didn't you realise that?
We have to defeat him by attacking
in the right wing.
You are still talking about Osman.
Ducas, didn't you say Osman's alps
are fighting better than our soldiers?
Right! But we have regular army.
Sultan's army is tired.
They have come a long way from Konya.
They'll be more tired tomorrow morning.
Do not abandon yourselves in despair!
We'll finish it tomorrow morning.
Do you understand me?
We couldn't outclass each other.
My army is tired.
Once we ruin Ducas' formation...
then our alps will hunt them.
We'll manage that
if Allah permits, my Sultan
You haven't give them a chance thanks to
your braveheart and ambition.
That formation...
will break.
I have no doubt, Osman Bey.
My Sultan, excuse me.
Karamanogullari are moving towards Konya.
If I do not go back to Konya
to stop them...
Konya will fall.
If I go back, you are going to be
weak...
against Byzantine.
If you go back, the fate of the
war will change, my Sultan.
What do you think, Osman Bey?
My Sultan...
The situation requires that you go back
to Konya.
How will you manage to defeat Ducas and
Nicola, Osman Bey?
With my Beys,
with my Ghazis...
we are going to do what we have to do
to break Ducas.
However...
If you don't go back to Konya...
That may be a bigger
problem for the state.
I'll go back.
I am giving the whole authority
to Osman Bey.
I won't be worrying myself, Osman Bey.
From now on, both my sword
and the honor of our state...
are in your hands, Osman Bey.
My Sultan.
Alps!
I am not your Bey today.
Your Bey will be fighting by your side...
in the name of Allah!
This is going to be a rough war..
If you love your life...
If you miss your family...
Go back now.
Here is the field, here is the
fierce enemy for those...
who want to fight!
You should know that until I end up
with either shahada or victory...
I will not leave the battlefield!
Either shahada or victory!
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest)
They are going to die shouting
their god's name!
Sultan is going back to Konya
but Osman didn't give up.
He never gives up.
Never.
A bloody victory is waiting
for us, Nicola.
Let's see where you are going...
what you are doing in secret, Zoe.
I'll learn eventually, Zoe.
Come on.
Alps!
Attack!
Sultan is leaving with his army. This
is not a hopeful war now.
It is impossible to fight against Byzantine
with a bunch of alps we have.
Wait a bit.
Osman Bey will arrive.
He must have something to say.
Be patient.
Nicola and Ducas must have already
learned that...
Sultan left with the army.
We are going to fight with Turan Tactic.
I am going to attack with my alps in the
shape of arrow in frontline.
Gunduz Bey and Umur Bey will not be
in the battlefield.
However, we are going to change the
fate of this war.
Are you going to attack a huge Army
with a bunch of alps, Osman Bey?
I am going to retreat when the fight
starts.
And we'll break Byzantine's formation.
The bloodshed will be red!
Alps!
Attack!
Cover!
Finally Osman!
Finally!
I see you turn tail and run!
I'll hang you in your tail in Sogut!
Wait.
Do not let them away!
Attack!
Cavalries, forward!
Finally, Osman.
Finally.
Gündüz Bey will attack in the left wing.
Umur Bey will attack in the right wing.
Also...
Also, you are not going to be alone.
Where did they come from?
Sultan is back in Konya.
However, he left some of his soldiers
under my order.
We are going to encircle them with...
We are going to use Turan Tactic(pincer
movement) against Byzantine.
We are going to let Nicola see
hell while he's alive!
It was a trap!
Nicola!
Dishonored dog!
- Cover the lord!
Get in the position!
Attack!
It's time, my Bey.
Alps!
Attack now!
Attack!
She went in this street before, Bala.
I lost her track later though.
So, this is where she has
been going.
Let's chase.
Wait a while.
It's ready, Zoe.
I stored it a long time, like wine,
just like how Nicola wanted.
I made it in my uterus like a infertile
mother who is yearning for a child.
It is going to be born in your
dexterious hands.
When you open and pour it to the meal...
it'll leave no sign in behind.
Nobody will know why Malhun Hatun's
child is dead.
Neither will they know she died aftermath.
She is not going to die as soon as
she swallow, is she?
Her baby will die first.
Such a woman like Malhun Hatun should
experience the grief of losing a child
with Osman Bey before she dies.
Of course she sould
experience that feeling.
I'll bury their pain in my body.
At the end, Malhun will die like
a crushed bug.
If Osman kisses those beautiful lips...
Osman will die too.
What are we going to do, Bala?
What's it?
You said you came to shed our blood.
We won't let you get away before
you try to shed our blood.
- Right, brother?
- Right.
We won't.
I'll give your bodies to my dogs
in the castle.
Let's see how you do that, freaking Lord!
You'll turn will come too.
Turanalp!
Hold on!
Shahada sherbet is...
very sweet, I understand it now.
"I bear witness that none
deserves worship except Allah, ...
and I bear witness that Muhammad
is the messenger of Allah."
He came for shahada, he reached
his goal.
He is a martry.
Thank my Lord.
When you die, there will be spring in
the land you spoiled!
You are going to die like your father's
goals did.
Come here once.
Come here.
I'll show you Turks won't stop until
we get freedom!
Turks never stop!
Enjoy your meal, Malhun Hatun.
Wait.
Sit here.
We can talk.
I don't want to eat alone.
You got tired all day.
Eat now, then you'll rest.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
What are you waiting for?
Eat.
Can I come in, Malhun Hatun?
Come in Bala Hatun!
Hi there.
Bala Hatun, what are you doing?
Eat!
I said eat, Zoe!
What does that mean Bala Hatun?
I said eat it.
What are you doing Bala Hatun.
This woman wants to poison you.
She poured venom in your meal.
She's lying.
You can eat it if you are telling the truth.
Otherwise I know what to do!
She obtained this poison...
which would kill you and my Bey's child
from a healer woman in Sogut.
Zoe wanted to give it to you.
Ah!
What are you doing?
What is happening?
Let me go! I am an old woman!
Tell me what you are after with Zoe.
Or I'll cut your throat.
Please don't. let me go.
Talk!
We caught the woman who prepared
the poison and put her in the caged tent
What is your intention?
Who are you working for?
Who made you do this?
Nicola!
Poor orphan girl, huh?
You disappointed me Zoe.
Gonca, put her in the caged tent too.
Come here.
Sit.
It's over.
Keep calm.
Osman Bey will punish them
when he is back.
I didn't believe you.
I thought you were being jealous.
I was such a fool.
If it weren't for you,
we'd lose our child.
Malhun Hatun.
Your child is my child too.
Always remember this.
Let being jealous aside...
I'd burn the whole world for your child.
We are not only Osman Bey's Hatuns...
and his soldiers to die in his path...
We are also the mothers of a glorious
state to be found.
Do not forget this.
Nicola!
Thank God!
Are you okay?
Helen, Helen, Ducas...
where are the others?
Ducas, Aknos, Yason, Feritles
all are dead!
Did Ducas die with his freaking
arrogance?
He repeated "Victory, victory, victory"
He gave us a massive defeat!
Helen...
Osman hit Emperor hard, Helen.
But there is something they don't know.
Both Emperor and his impertinent son
need me now!
A new era is starting.
I am stronger than ever before!
I am stronger now.
Helen.
Set off.
You'll arrive in the castle by the morning.
On foot.
Nicola!
Osman Bey is coming!
My Bey is coming!
Masha Allah! (praise be)
You didn't disappointed me with the
swords I made for you!
O Allah, I beg to You
the good which
Your Prophet Muhammad (ﷺ)
begged of You
Masha Allah! (praise be)
Today...
we fought for our future.
Thank my Lord...
we are back in Ertugrul Ghazi's tent
with victory!
Long live Osman Bey!
This victory is all of ours!
It is the victory of mothers who send
their Beys, their valiant sons to war...
It is the victory of scholar elders!
This is your victory!
This victory is the preview
of a glorious state...
under whose flag
the Islam will gather up
However, always remember this.
It is always harder to protect a recently
conquered land...
thank conquering a new place!
So, with our factories that we'll build...
with our mosques in which we'll pray...
with the whole future of ours...
We are going to make this land our state.
We watered this land with our blood!
The state we are going to found...
will be fighting for justice!
We will not stand back in front
of injustice!
Our state shall be everlasting with
our community...
and our justice in Allah's name!
May Allah bless you.
You conquered the enemy with your sword.
You conquered the hearts
with your justice.
With this victory...
you changed the fate of a whole community,
Osman Bey.
Thank you Master Davut.
Thank you.
Ahmet Alp.
Thank lord you are back safe and sound.
Thank you Hatun.
I hope you are fine.
I am, don't worry.
Thank Lord you are back safe
and sound, father.
I am yearning for a grandchild, daughter.
How can I not come back?
Masha Allah! (praise be)
Your victories shall never end, Osman Bey.
Thank you Malhun Hatun.
Thank you Bala.
Thank Lord that we see these days.
Your happiness circled our tent.
May Allah keep you with us, my Bey.
I married twice.
As I saw you together...
this is your victory too.
Thank my Lord.
Osman Bey.
We want to talk to you
if you are available, my Bey.
Of course.
Let's talk.
- My Bey.
- My Gonca.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Thank Lord you are back safe and sound.
May our war be blessed.
Amin.
What are you thinking like a little owl?
I was thinking if my share of the booty
would be enough for your dowery or not.
How about that?
You are a dark horse!
Who is that lucky Hatun?
Tell me, I want to learn.
She is someone...
...who doesn't realise
how valiant she is...
She is the Sultan of my heart.
Alaca Hatun.
Where is Zoe?
I couldn't see her.
Do you know where she is?
Tell me.
Bala Hatun saved our child's life.
You saved both Malhun Hatun's and
our child's life.
May Allah bless you Bala Hatun.
What is going to happen to that old woman
and Zoe, my Bey?
What happens to the babykillers
will happen to them!
Goktug!
To my Bey's Hatun...
with a baby in her belly, huh?
What a snake you are!
What is going to happen to me?
You'll die by the poison you made!
No! No!
Do not hamper Alps!
Eat and...
die!
Goktug!
Save me.
Save me!
Goktug! Do not leave, my Goktug!
Do not leave me alone!
Goktug!
Masha Allah! (praise be)
Salam Aleikum
(peace be upon you).
Alaikum Salam
(you too) Osman Bey.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Here.
Your eyes are lightened by a divine light.
Osman Bey.
Like how you waited with patience for
your child to born...
Both the birth of your child that
you waited in patience...
... and the state you wanted to found
are coming.
Inshallah, Inshallah.
(If Allah permits).
Even if I am left alone...
As Ertugrul Ghazi's son Osman Bey...
I'll die fighting in the name of Allah.
Your patience, your ambition, your faith...
made you a scholar.
Thank you, thank you.
In the war you fought against Byzantine...
the wind of the victory of yours was your...
biggest supporter.
It relieved your community, Osman Bey.
Eyvallah (thank you).
Not only this wind helped you
gather all the Turks in your land...
But also the towns, the cities
the tents of yours developed.
I hope I and my breed can conquer
lots of towns and...
develop them like our towns.
You won the fight in the battlefield.
You killed Byzantine.
They are not going to be able to
get their head out...
of their castles and challange you.
You embraced seventy two nations.
You opened your heart to them.
This is founding a state.
May my Lord be with you in this path.
Amin. Amin, insha Allah.
We are just getting started.
We are going to lighten our way with
Islam and perform our goals.
Do not forget.
Your aim was shown...
in your dream that was given to you,
Osman Bey.
Like Yusuf Has Hacb from Balasabun said:
"You shall follow your heart"
You shall always be fair...
in wherever you go.
in and wherever you conquer.
Inshallah Inshallah (if Allah permits).
Perhaps you'll have a greater position
than a Bey.
The state that was shown to you in your
dream shall be yours!
Amin.
That moon came out of your chest
in your dream...
shall be the light of your breed
who dominate earth!
Alaca! Alaca, my waters break!
Notify Bala Hatun!
Notify Osman Bey, he is in Sogut.
Calm down, sit here.
Hurry up Alaca!
Oh my Lord, give a propitious child
to my Bey.
A propitious child.
This is a miracle of Allah, Bala Hatun.
Bala Hatun run!
Malhun Hatun is giving birth.
Hurry up!
My Bala, are you okay?
ı am.
Hurry up!
Osman Bey!
Tell me.
Malhun Hatun.
It's time.
What?
Ya Allah!
Malhun, hold on.
Hope is coming.
What a lucky child we have! A brave father,
and two mothers are waiting for him/her.
Come on. Hurry up!
Push.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate)
Push.
Masha Allah! (praise be)
Masha Allah! ​(praise be)
Brother!
Tell me.
What is the situation?
She is about to give birth, brother.
Masha Allah! ​(praise be)
Allah will give us children too, Hatun.
Not one, not three, not five...
We should pray for propitious children,
Cerkutay.
Inshallah, apple of my eye.
Inshallah. (if Allah permits)
My Lord...
Give me a good child for my breed.
May you grant my
Bala with a child as well.
You son has been born safe and sound,
Osman Bey.
His mother and he are fine.
Bala...
I gave you a son, Osman Bey.
You didn't give me only a son...
you gave me the whole world.
Take him. Hug your son.
Your yearning heart must feel him.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate)
Thank my Lord.
Thank Lord.
Daughter.
You prayed a lot, you have been patient.
Now you shall be patient
against this situation too.
No doubt that your Lord
is hearing you. is seeing you.
Allah hears our prayers.
Now...
I want to name him Orhan.
What is the meaning of Orhan,
Osman Bey?
The one who conquers a lot...
The one who founds cities...
The one who is fair.
You gave his name.
May Allah give him a long life.
May his name suits him,
may his fate be good, inshallah.
Allah is the greatest.
I bear witness that there is
no god except the One Allah.
I bear witness that Muhammad is the
messenger of Allah.
Hurry to the prayer.
Hurry to salvation.
Allah is the greatest.
There is no god except the One Allah.
I bear witness that there is
no god except the One Allah.
I bear witness that Muhammad is the
messenger of Allah.
Hurry to the prayer.
Hurry to salvation.
Prayer is better than sleep.
Allah is the greatest.
There is no god except the One Allah.
Your name is Orhan.
Hey son!
Your name was given by Ertugrul
Ghazi's son Osman Bey, your father.
May Allah give you a long life.
The angel in the sky and the people
on the ground shall know that..
your name... your name is Orhan.
Mashallah, Mashallah(praise be) my Orhan.
My Bala!
You look pale, what is it?
My Sheik father's tale came true.
I am pregnant Osman Bey.
Bala?!
What are you saying?
We'll have child?
Is that true, my Bala?
Yes! I am pregnant!
Hey Masha Allah (praise be)
Allah Allah!
Masha Allah! (praise be)
Bala!
Bala! I told you!
Our Lord hears our prayers!
Yes, you told me.
It was a test, Osman Bey.
We went patient. Our prayers came true.
Yes!
Our children will fight
should to shoulder!
Our children will carry the banner
of Ertugrul Ghazi...
and crush the cruels with that banner!
Inshallah Osman Bey.
Inshallah.
I am happy for Orhan that he won't be
alone to carry on your goals.
My Bala.
It is time to stand up.
It is time to found a state...
and kneel the whole world down!
It is time to take root like a
glorious tree.
Now, it is time to found a state!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com